<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weiyi (Max) Zhang</title>
    <link>https://optimalzhang.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Weiyi (Max) Zhang</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://optimalzhang.github.io/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://optimalzhang.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://optimalzhang.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a Research Scientist at the Networking and Service Quality Management (N&amp;amp;SQM) Research organization, AT&amp;amp;T Labs Research, the research organization of AT&amp;amp;T,
which was part of Bell Laboratories before 1996 and part of AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories afterward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before joining the AT&amp;amp;T Labs, I was an Assistant Professor at the Computer Science Department, North Dakota State University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have 100 refereed papers published/accepted in my research areas, including more than 30 publications in prestigious journals such as
IEEE/ACM Transactions on Networking, IEEE Transactions on Vehicular Technology, IEEE Journal on Selected Areas in Communications,
IEEE/OSA Journal of Optical Communications and Networking, ACM Wireless Networks, and ACM Mobile Networks &amp;amp; Applications.
I have also published more than 60 papers in internationally reputable conferences such as IEEE INFOCOM, ICNP, ICDCS, and ACM MobiHoc.
I received the Best Paper Award in 2007 from IEEE Global Communications Conference (GLOBECOM), the Best Paper Award from IEEE ICC&amp;rsquo;2014,
and the Best Paper Award from IEEE ICNP&amp;rsquo;2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to both Google Scholar and ResearchGate, my research works have received more than 2000 citations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been serving on editorial boards and technical/organization committees for reputable journals and conferences, such as IEEE IoT Journal and IEEE INFOCOM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With my wife, our sons (Marco and Lewen) and our curious pet bunny, I have lived on the West Coast (there, there, and there), the Midwest (there), and the East Coast (here and here) of the USA.I have years&amp;rsquo; experience of living with extreme weathers, from triple-digit deadly hot Arizona to double-digit below freezing North Dakota.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Erdos Number is 3.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
